CURRICULUM VITAE

DEEPAK SHARMA

Contact no. 8408811234

Email: - d23sharma@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic individual with 10 years' experience in a fast-moving Business Process Outsourcing (BPO) industry seeking to start a career by join your team as a self-taught front-end web developer, looking for full-time front-end junior developer role in order to apply front-end development skills to deliver coding excellence.

Hoping to combine excellent customer service skills, technical knowledge and attention to detail to provide an exciting and easy-to-use web experience for users.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- HTML
- CSS
- Java Script basic
- iQuery
- Bootstrap
- SASS
- NPM
- Github

CERTIFICATIONS:

Name : Responsive Web DesignIssues by: freecodecamp.com

Issued date: 02/ July/ 2022

Name : Web Design Expert

Issues by: Universal Informatics (Janzeerwala campus Indore)

Issued date: 25/ Feb/ 2021

Project URL:

- https://d23sharma.github.io/portfolio/
- https://d23sharma.github.io/sheertech/
- https://d23sharma.github.io/netflix/
- https://d23sharma.github.io/Landing-page/
- https://d23sharma.github.io/bootcamp/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

TELEPERFORMANCE, INDORE,

22 APR 2019 – 02 APR 2021

Technical support executive

About Teleperformance:

Teleperformance is the worldwide leader in outsourced omnichannel customer experience management. Teleperformance connects the biggest and most respected brands on the planet with their customers by providing customer care, technical support, customer acquisition, digital solutions, analytics, back-office and other specialized services to ensure consistently positive customer interactions.

Responsibilities

- Serves as a initial point of contact for customers with complaints, queries, request, and feedbacks for Yahoo Small Business support currently known as Verizon Small Business.
- Ensures that all the technical and billing related request, queries and complaint are responded in a timely and professional manner via calls, e-mails and chat
- Following up with clients to ensure the problem is resolved.
- Troubleshooting technical issues starting from password reset, set up one or more e-mail account, assisting with website design and development using in-house tool called Website Builder
- Installation of SSL certificates to secure the website, performing DNS transfers and setup on behalf of clients as well as troubleshooting DNS issues.
- After completion of 6 month in the process, moved to the premium queue of Merchant stores
 where I used to deal with E-commerce store owners and assist them with issues concerning
 online orders.
- Assist with Edit store, order processing, Store statistics, order delivery and their notifications to both parties (buyer & seller), product promotions e.t.c

MountN Marketing Solutions Pvt Ltd

DEC 2017- JAN 2019

Team Leader

About MountN Marketing solutions

It was a start up providing services in the field of Marketing (B2B demand generation, helps our clients create pipeline and accelerate revenue by identifying, profiling, nurturing and connecting with the decision makers within their targeted customer & prospect accounts), Information technology (Website creation, development & maintenance) & business consulting

Responsibilities

- Handling a team of 24 agents.
- Setting up targets and marketing strategy
- Managing relationships & attending meetings with service providers via Skype...
- Managing online inquiries
- Submitting daily conversion report to Managing director
- Conducting training sessions, Quality sessions, Mock call sessions to improveperformance

Achievements:

Team Size grew from 4 to 25 within six months

Monthly Revenue increased on an average from \$600.00 a month to \$22000.00 a month.

CREDENCE RESOURCE MANAGEMENT

04 NOV 2014 to 11 APR 2017

Customer Service Executive - Operations

About CRM

Credence Resource Management, LLC is a best-in-class partner that delivers exceptional performance through cost-effective Accounts Receivable Management and Revenue Cycle Solutions.

- World-class first party customer care, technical support, delinquency prevention, and collection services.
- High performance early and late stage debt recovery solutions through your revenuecycle
- Integrated legal, bankruptcy, and probate support
- Insurance eligibility verification, claims submission, follow-up, and post copay anddenial collections.

Responsibilities

- Receiving Inbound calls & inform about delinquency on T-MOBILE Postpay accounts.
- Create urgency on billed amount which were not recovered before cancellations ofservices through the tools provided by the company.
- Responsible for reporting daily revenue report to the team leader.
- Handling second voice of team mates & managing their performances.
- Handling OJT batches, providing product knowledge, giving feedback, taking second voice forthem.
- Responsible for achieving daily targets.

Achievements:

Best performer for the quarter April to June 2015.

HUTCHISON 3 GLOBAL SERVICES, PUNE, MH, INDIA

08 AUG 2013 - 20 OCT 2014

Customer relations advisor

About Hutchison 3 Global services Ltd:

Three UK is a British telecommunications and internet service provider operating as a subsidiary of CK Hutchison Holdings, operating under the global Three brand. The company launched in March 2003 as the United Kingdom's first commercial video mobile network. It provides 3G and 4G services through its own network infrastructure.

Responsibilities

- Receiving inbound calls as the first line of support for billing, network issues & faulty devices concerns
- Troubleshooting of dongle & handset faults like: Network coverage issues, internet connectivity issues, browser issues etc
- Also identifying if the 3 dongle or handset is faulty and arranged to get it fixed through proper channels.
- Upselling of newly launched packages for handset & sim only plans.
- Redirecting customers to the concerned department after initial checks & troubleshooting.
- Handling customer retentions by understanding the requirements.

WIPRO BPO LIMITED, PUNE, MH

19 JAN 2010 - 01 AUG 2013

Associate

About Wipro:

Wipro BPO, the Business Process Outsourcing service line of Wipro Technologies, is one of the largest BPO service providers on a global delivery platform. Wipro BPO has the capabilities to provide onshore, nearshore, offshore and hybrid delivery options with operations in more than 28 centers in 11 countries. The services portfolio spans industry specific solutions in Customer Contact center (technical and non-technical; voice and non-voice), Finance and Accounting outsourcing, Human Resource outsourcing, Supply chain management, Knowledge services including Data Management and reporting, Legal process outsourcing, and Sales and Marketing outsourcing

Responsibilities:

- Receiving inbound calls for Flight tickets reservation, itinerary change, cancellations, refund.
- Take care of the passengers with confirmed booking on United airlines flights as well as other airlines flight in case of Irregular Operations
- Receive calls from passengers, partner airlines officials as well as travel agents to help them book tickets
- Provide information for flight details, baggage query, sitting arrangement.
- Handling OJT batches, doing floor support, take escalation calls on the operations floor.

Achievements:

Maintaining call quality 90% throughout the year

TELEPERFORMANCE, INDORE, MP

10 SEP 2007 - 15 DEC 2008

Customer care executive

About Teleperformance:

Teleperformance is the worldwide leader in outsourced omnichannel customer experience management. Teleperformance connects the biggest and most respected brands on the planet with their customers by providing customer care, technical support, customer acquisition, digital solutions, analytics, back-office and other specialized services to ensure consistently positive customer interactions.

Responsibilities

- Receiving inbound calls for domestic network service provider Airtel.
- Taking care of the customer's queries and complaints related with charges on the pre
 paid connections and providing refunds for the invalid charges after following a
 thorough procedure as per the process' requirement.
- Providing information on VAS (Value added services) & setting up, deactivating & making changes to their current VAS as per their needs.
- Offering assistance with troubleshooting on the network related issues & handset issue

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

- Secondary School Certificate (SSC) Examination in 2003 from MP Board
- Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC) Examination in 2005 from MP Board

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name: Mr. Om Prakash Sharma

Date of Birth : 23-04-1987

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Religion : Hindu

Languages Know: English, Hindi